抱歉  各位  这出戏...
Excuse me, folks, this is a...
不对外开放  我们知道  可我们是猴子的朋友
Closed set. We know. But we're friends with the monkey.
早
Good morning.
伙计  你看我带谁来了
Hey pal, look who I brought.
是你的老朋友  小象哈里
It's your old friend Harry Elefante.
真不给面子
Whoa, dude. Burn!
我不懂
I don't get it.
它昨天看到我还很高兴的样子
He seemed so happy to see me yesterday.
别放在心上
Don't take it personal.
它近来压力很大
He's under a lot of pressure,
主演电影什么的
you know, starring in a movie and all.
马塞尔现在到底有多大牌
Now just how big of a star is Marcel?
换做是人的话  就好比...
In human terms? I'd say...
斯碧尔·谢波德
... Cybill Shepherd.
你们这身装束  是要出演电影  还是真怕染上病毒
So you guys in the movie or you just really paranoid?
沙尔
Hey, Sal?
杰利问  猴子可以上地铁那一幕了吗
Jerry wants to know if the monkey's ready for the subway set?
请问
Excuse me?
杰利是导演吗  哪一个
Jerry is the director? Which one's he?
-坐在导演椅子那个  -知道了
- The one in the director's chair? - Gotcha.
菲比  我们走
Pheebs, walk with me.
好  我为什么要跟你走
OK. Um, how come I'm walking with you?
我们往这里走是为了远离那些...
We're just going over here so that we can get away from...
可怕的食肉病毒
...the horrible flesh-eating virus!
看在老天的份上  听我说
For the love of God, woman, listen to me!
他有没有在看  他在看吗
Is he looking? Is he looking?
-我遇到麻烦了 -给我说说
- We've got a problem. - Tell me.
我没办法帮克里斯化妆
I can't do Chris' makeup.
她不肯承认她有胡子
She refuses to acknowledge her mustache.
-很严重吗  -像眉毛掉到嘴上似的  - 懂了
- ls it bad? - lt looks like her eyebrow fell down. - Got it.
除非有人说服她  让我帮她漂白
Now unless someone convinces her to let me bleach it,
不然尚格·云顿就得跟大胡子亲热了
Jean-Claude Van Damme is gonna be making out with Gabe Kaplan.
我去跟她谈谈
I'll talk to her.
我讨厌演员
I hate actors.
老兄  伪装得不错  我差点没看到你
Nice camouflage man, for a minute there I almost didn't see ya.
请问
Excuse me.
你是叫钱德勒吗
Is your name Chandler?
对  没错
Yes, it is.
钱德勒·宾
Chandler Bing.
你认识我  还是你很会钓男人
Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?
我是苏西·莫斯
I'm Susie Moss.
四年级时  戴眼镜
Fourth grade? Glasses?
我常像拿手提包一样拿着包动物饼干
I used to carry a box of animal crackers like a purse?
苏西·莫斯
Susie Moss!
是你啊
Right! Yeah! Wow!
你真是
You look....
女大十八变
Great job growing up.
很高兴看到你不戴那顶缀满小镜子的牛仔帽了
It's nice to see you don't still wear that denim cap with the mirrors on it.
对  升上五年级之后  我发现我不是个拉皮条的
Right. I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.
记得我们班表演的话剧吗
Remember the class play?
你掀我的裙子  全礼堂的人都看到我的内裤了
You pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium saw my underpants?
对  那个时候  我用幽默方式来保护自己
Yes. Back then, I used humor as a defense mechanism.
谢天谢地  我现在改邪归正了
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
-天啊  -怎么了
- Oh, my God! - What? What?
是尚格·云顿
It's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
我不知道他也出演这部电影  他好帅
I didn't know he was in this movie. He is so hot!
真的吗
You think?
布鲁塞尔肌肉男  枭雄尚格·云顿
The Muscles from Brussels? Wham-Bam-Van-Damme?
你看过《时空特警》吗
Did you see Time Cop?
没有  他在戏里有什么专长吗
No. Was he any good in it?
瑞秋  他完全改变了时空
Rachel, Rachel, he like, totally changed time.
-那你还不过去跟他讲话  -说得容易
- So why don't you go talk to him? - Yeah.
你过去告诉他他很可爱 又能怎么样
What, so you go over there, you tell him you think he's cute, what's the worst that could happen?
他会听到的
He could hear me.
-好吧  我去替你讲  -瑞秋  你敢  别
- OK, I'm doin' it for ya. - Rachel don't, don't you dare, don't!
别去
Don't!
说我是厨师
Tell him I cook!
对不起
Excuse me.
这样会有一点怪怪的
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...
我那边那个朋友
... but my friend over there...
对了  她是个厨师
...who cooks, by the way....
她觉得你很可爱
She thinks you're cute.
你不这么觉得吗
You don't think I'm cute?
我不知道
I don't know.
你觉得你可爱吗
Do you think you're cute?
我们扯太远了  我是过来告诉你
We're getting off the track. I was supposed to tell you...
我朋友她觉得你很可爱
... my friend thinks you're cute.
我该怎么告诉她呢
So what should I tell her?
你可以告诉她  我觉得她的朋友很可爱
You can tell her I think her friend is cute.
-化妆  -叫我了  我得走了
- Makeup! - That's me. I gotta go.
好
O.K.
我得碰你老兄的手多少次  你才会开尊口约我出去呢
So, listen. How many times must I touch you on the arm before you ask me on a date?
我想再试一次
Well, let's try one more.
好了  八点"厄尼"餐厅见
There you go. Ernie's, 8:00?
我会赴约
I'll be there.
谁知道  一切顺利的话  或许这一次
And who knows, if things go well, maybe this time
我能看到你的内裤
... I'll get to see your underwear.
没人听到这句话吗
No one was around to hear that?
他怎么说
So what'd he say?
他真浑蛋
What a jerk!
我一直在跟他谈你  可是他却一直想要约我
I kept talking about you, and he kept asking me out.
我当然是拒绝了
Naturally, you know, I said no.
还是谢了
Thanks, anyway.
但是他一直约我
He just kept asking...
一而再  再而三...
...and asking, asking, asking....
瑞秋  如果你想跟他约会  就去好了
Rachel, if you, if you want to go out with him, you can.
虽然对我可能不太好  但你要是想...
Sound like a big jerk to me but if that's what you want to do...
尚格  她说好  今晚见
Jean-Claude, she said yes! I'll see you tonight!
谢谢
Thank you.
然后  尚格带我去了《十字路口》拍摄现场
And then Jean-Claude took me to that place Crossroads...
我们在那里跟德鲁·巴里摩尔玩在了一起
and that's where we hung out with Drew Barrymore.
老兄  她绝对正点
Oh, man. She's so smokin'!
她有对最丰满的...
She's got the greatest set of...
这里没男的
No guys around, huh?
-有谁需要什么吗  -我要杯浓缩咖啡
- Does anybody need anything? - I'll have an espresso.
我自己来吧
Actually, I'll get it.
叫你去的话  说不定最后会被你喝掉
If I ask you to, you'll end up drinking it yourself.
-好过分  -我知道
- That is so unfair. - I know.
你跟云顿那样对她之后  你还要喝她的咖啡
Like you'd drink her coffee after what you did to her with Van Damme?
乔伊  我要取消今晚的壁球
Joey, I have to cancel racquetball tonight.
马塞尔的训练师刚来电  他会让马塞尔陪我几小时
That was Marcel's trainer. He's gonna let me have him for a couple of hours.
你为了猴子失我的约
You're blowing me off for a monkey?
我们可以改到周六
We can reschedule for Saturday.
对  除非你搭上一票鸽子
Yeah, unless you hook up with a bunch of pigeons.
用叉子戳我
Stick a fork in me...
我熟了
... I am done!
用叉子干什么
Stick a fork what?
像你煎牛排那样
Like when you're cooking a steak.
好吧  我不吃肉
O.K. I don't eat meat.
那你怎么知道菜熟了呢
How do you know vegetables are done?
不知道啊  只要吃一口就知道了
Well, you don't. You eat them and you can tell.
那吃我吧  我熟了
Okay, then eat me, I'm done!
这个女人真是无可挑剔
I've met the perfect woman.
我们坐在沙发上  正在亲热
We're sitting on her couch, fooling around...
突然她转过来对我说
...and then she turns to me and says:
"你想过在电梯里做吗"
"Did you ever want to do it in an elevator?"
那你说什么
What did you say?
我相信我的回答是"呦嘻呼啦"
I believe my exact words were 'Flaign,en - sten'.
我不知道该说什么  你怎么知道你想不想在电梯里做
I mean I didn't know what to say, how do you know if you wanna do it on an elevator?
你就是知道
You just know.
该死  我们得走了  我定了30分钟后的位子
Shoot. We gotta go. Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
不不不
Oh no no no no, no no no no no no,
我的计划最多不会超过两三分钟的
you see, what I had planned shouldn't take more that 2, 3 minutes tops.
两百秒钟的激情  我们得走了
Two hundred seconds of passion! We gotta go.
但是
But...
我有个主意
... here's an idea.
你有没有穿过女人的内裤
Have you ever worn women's underwear?
实际上穿过
Well, yes, actually...
是我艾德娜姑妈的
... but they were my Aunt Edna's.
一条裤子里挤了三个人
And there were three of us in there.
我在想  如果你今天吃晚饭时
I was thinking it would be kind of sexy...
穿我的内裤  会很性感
...if you wore mine tonight at dinner.
你要我穿你内裤
You want me to wear your panties?
可以吗
Could you?
如果我穿了你内裤
If I was wearing your underwear...
那你穿什么
...then what would you be wearing?
你真棒
You're swell!
你看  我做了马塞尔最喜欢吃的餐点  香蕉蛋糕
Check it out. I made Marcel's favorite dish, banana cake...
加了虫子
...with mealworm.
蜡烛
Candle.
今天晚上可有盼头了
What do you think's gonna happen here tonight?
喂  你好  你们过来了  还是...
Hello. Hi, are you on your way over or...
不会  我了解  猴子也得工作
No, I understand. A monkey's gotta work.
不  小事一桩
No, it's no big deal.
我又没什么特别的计划
It's not like I had anything special planned.
好  好  好  再见
OK. OK. OK. Bye.
好  瑞秋  你先说吧
O.K. Rachel, why don't you start talking first?
好吧  我觉得她太无理取闹了
Alright. I feel that this is totally unjustified.
她先同意的  我又没做什么...
She gave me the green light, I did nothing that..
你以为我不能通过电视机看到你吗
Do you think I can't see you in the TV set?
好了  摩妮卡  你有什么话想说的...
All right, Monica. If there's something you'd like to share...
你没有权利跟他出去
You had no right to go out with him!
-太荒唐了吧  -你出卖我
- That's the most ridiculous... - You sold me out!
-我才没有出卖你呢  -有  你有
- I did not! - You absolutely
你让我讲好不好
Would you let me talk!
你刚弹我的头
Did you just flick me?
你不让我说完  而我只是...
Well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was...
好痛
That hurt!
别弹了
Quit flicking!
你别弹了
You stop flicking!
是你先弹的
You flicked me first!
别这样
Let's not do this!
冷静点
Calm.
想点快乐的事
Happy thoughts!
冷静点
Calm.
老娘要出马了
Now I'm gonna kick some ass!
好吧  你们住手  我就放手
All right. Now, I will let go if you both stop.
你要我不再见他吗  你是想这样吗
You want me to stop seeing him? Is that what you want?
你要我打电话给他  告诉他你要替我跟他约会吗
You want me to just tell him you're seeing him instead?
-你是想这样吗  -好啊
- Is that what you want? - O.K.
-原来你想这样  -对
- That's what you want? - Yes.
-好  -好
- Fine! - Fine!
这不就得了
There we go.
我们要是在牢里的话  就会沦为我的女人
If we were in prison, you guys would be, like, my bitches.
各位  谢谢你们今晚带上我
Thanks for letting me tag along tonight, you guys.
客气什么
Forget about it.
你觉得怎么样  扭动先生
How you doing there, squirmy?
我窝在里面
I'm hanging in.
有一点出来
And a little out.
你是导演的助理
So assistant to the director?
这工作多带劲  你一定有很多有意思的职责
That's an exciting job. You must have a ton of cool responsibilities
我跟选角完全无关
I have nothing to do with casting.
你们大家想吃什么
So what are you guys gonna eat?
为什么我满脑子都想着把那冰块放进嘴里
How come all I can think about is putting that ice in my mouth...
然后舔遍你的全身
...and licking you all over?
因为我的高中是男校  现在神要补偿我
Because I went to an all-boys high school, and God is making up for it?
我现在就要你
I want you right here...
就在这里
... right now.
现在  在这里
Right now, right here?
你不认为这里是公共场所吗
Don't you think we're in kind of a public place?
这里还真有虾
They do have the shrimp.
我在洗手间等你
Meet me in the bathroom.
现在我要去洗手间了
I'm going to the bathroom now.
快来
Come on.
好  先生
All right, mister.
亮出你的内裤
Let's see those panties.
遵命
Alrighty.
你知道怎么样会更性感吗
But you know what would be even sexier?
怎么样
What?
你没把你的衬衫塞进去的话
If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.
好  现在呢  我想看你只穿内裤
All right. Now, I would like to see you wearing nothing but them.
把衣服脱了
Take your clothes off.
好吧  但你要知道  这样我们会错过特色菜介绍
O.K. But I hope you realize this means we'll miss hearing about the specials.
快  速度
Come on, hurry!
你要讲求速度还是讲求质量
Do you want this done quick or done right?
好  转过去  我要看你的后面
All right, turn around. I wanna see you from behind.
有人一直在跟着"钢铁翘臀"视频练习啊
Somebody's been doing his Buns of Steel video.
那你要我缩紧什么吗  或是...
So you want me to clench anything or...?
苏西
Susie?
总算报了四年级的仇
This is for the fourth grade.
-什么意思  -什么"什么意思"
- What do you mean? - What do I mean?
你说什么意思
What do you mean, what do I mean?!
意思是内裤  先生  我就是这意思
I mean underpants, mister! That's what I mean!
什么  什么意思
What? What do you mean?
我的裙子
My skirt...
你掀开了  大家笑了
...you lifted. Kids laughing!
"内裤苏西"的外号一直跟到我18岁
I was Susie Underpants till I was 18!
都是四年级的事了  你怎会还耿耿于怀
That was in fourth grade! How could you still be upset about that?
不如二十年后你再打电话告诉我是不是还耿耿于怀
Why don't you call me in 20 years and tell me if you're still upset about this.
要知道  你这条内裤是要不回来了
I hope you realize you're not getting these underpants back!
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
两个礼拜前  我还在看《绝命杀阵》
Just like two weeks ago, I was watching Sudden Death...
现在我竟然在跟尚格·云顿约会
...and now I'm on a date with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
-你能痛扁那个人吗  -能
- Can you beat up that guy? - Yeah.
-你能痛扁那个人吗  -当然
- Can you beat up that guy? - Sure.
真是太疯狂了
This is so wild.
我承认你同意跟我约会让我很吃惊
I gotta admit, I was surprised that you agreed to go on a blind date.
通常我是不会答应的
Normally, I would not do it.
那你为什么会为我破例呢
What made you make the exception for me?
因为瑞秋告诉我说
Because Rachel told me...
你很想跟我和德鲁·巴里摩尔3P
...you were dying to have a threesome with me and Drew Barrymore.
对了  德鲁有一些规矩  而且
By the way, Drew has some ground rules and....
-给我道歉  -不
- Say you're sorry! - No.
道歉  瑞秋
Say it! Rachel.
不  休想
No! I'm not gonna!
道歉  道歉  好极了
Say it! Say it! Great!
瑞秋  道歉  不然你的毛衣就遭殃了
Rachel. Say you're sorry or your sweater gets it.
那是我最喜欢的毛衣  我第三次约会的毛衣
That is my favorite sweater! That is my third-date sweater!
给我道歉
Say you're sorry.
你想玩是吧  好  我陪你玩
You wanna play? Okay, let's play.
我陪你玩
Let's play.
你想怎么样
What are you gonna do?
把毛衣还给我  不然我就酱腌皮包
Give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.
你才没这胆
You don't have the guts.
是吗  起码我不会没胆告诉哪个男人  我觉得他很可爱
Yeah? At least I wasn't too chicken to tell some guy I thought he was cute.
住手  别发疯了
Stop! Stop the madness!
这也太过头了
This is crazy!
你们谁还记得最初吵架的原因
Who can remember why you started fighting in the first place?
对  没错
Yes, that's right.
但是
But still....
看看你的皮包
Look at your purse!
看看你的毛衣
Look at your sweater!
看看你们自己
Look at yourselves!
我会帮你补毛衣的
I'll help you fix your sweater.
我会帮你
I'll help you...
丢掉皮包
...throw out your purse.
对不起  我阻止了你们约会
I'm sorry that I made you stop seeing him.
对不起  我明知道你喜欢他还跟他约会
I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked him.
对不起  我借了你的手套
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
乔伊
Joey?
妈
Ma?
乔伊
Joey?
钱德勒
Chandler?
你怎么还在这里  我还以为你们走了
What're you still doin' here? I thought you guys took off.
不不不  她走了  还带走了我的衣服
No, no, no. She took off with my clothes!
-你裸着吗  -也不全裸
- Are you naked in there? - Well, not exactly.
我穿着女式内裤
I'm wearing panties.
你总穿女式内裤吗
You always wear panties?
不  这是第一次
No, no. This is the first time.
你还真够倒霉
Talk about your bad luck!
第一次试女式内裤  衣服就被别人拿走了
The first time you try panties and someone walks off with your clothes.
不是我要穿的  是苏西叫我穿的
I was not trying them out. Susie asked me to wear them.
-让我看看  -不要
- Let me see! - No.
我才不让你或任何人看呢
I'm not letting you or anybody else see, ever!
好吧  好吧
All right, all right!
有人在用牙线
Someone's flossing!
乔伊  有些人不喜欢那样的
Joey, some people don't like that.
钱德勒穿着女式内裤
Chandler's wearing panties.
什么
What?
-让我看  -不  还是别看了
- Let me see! - No,no. You don't have to see!
你好  屁屁
Hi, tushy!
你们谁把内裤借我穿
Alright. One of you give me your underpants.
-不行  -帮不上忙  我没穿内裤
- Oh, no. - Can't help you, I'm not wearing any.
你怎么可以不穿内裤
How can you not be wearing any underwear?
穿桃红色丁字裤的人倒训起人来了
I'm getting heat from the guy in the hot pink thong.
听我说  罗斯  我出五十块买你的内裤
Look, Ross. I'll give you $50 for your underpants.
-菲比  你倒完牛奶给我好吗  -我快好了
- Pheebs, can I have the milk after you? - I'm almost done with it.
别急  裤子提好了
Keep your panties on.
我上电影屏幕了
And I'm in the movie!
-怎么了  -有个感染病毒的人请病假
- What happened? - A virus victim called in sick...
所以凯西就推荐我上场  我要死在担架上了
...so Cathy recommended me and boom! I'm dying on a gurney!
罗斯  马塞尔刚拍完最后一场戏
Ross, Marcel just finished his last scene,
你可以去片场和它道别
if you wanna go down there and say goodbye.
没关系  他说不定还要去庆功宴什么的
That's okay. He's probably got parties to go to and stuff.
它继续它的生活了  生活就是这样子  对不对
He's moved on. That's the way it goes, right?
天啊
Oh, my God!
怎么了
What?
*看来我们成功了*
*Looks like we made it*
*成功忘记对方*
*Left each other on the way*
*找到新欢*
*to another love*
*看来我们成功了*
*Looks like we made it*
*今天以前  我还如是想*
*Or I thought so, till today*
*直到看到你为止*
*Until you were there, everywhere*
*看到你  往日回忆涌上心头*
*And all I could taste was Love the way we made it*
*看来我们成功了*
*Looks like we made it*
我想写首歌记录这件事
I think I want to write a song about all this.
只是我的吉他有条弦断了
Except one of the strings on my guitar is broken.
钱德勒  你的G弦借我好吗
Chandler, can I borrow your G-string?
-你这句话憋很久了吧  -大概20分钟吧
- How long you been waiting to say that? - About 20 minutes!
你们看不出来吗  这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
停
Cut!
你们看不出来吗  这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
停
Cut!
你们看不出来吗  这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
妈咪
Mommy!
你们看不出来吗  这个人死了
Can't you see what's going on? This man is dead!